Lynn Mora

E-Commerce Corporate Manager at Libertador Hotels, Resorts & Spas + Digital Disruptor + Travel Geek

lynnmora@gmail.com

Summary

Online marketing, data & statistical analytics, ecommerce and revenue management. Deep knowledge of SEO, SEM, CRM, Programatic Advertising, consumer behavior, Scrum, Agile. Currently learning more about data science, machine learning. Computer science dropout that ended graduating as a marketer, now pursuing a Masters degree. Built and ran my own startup, so I'm familiar with PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Apache servers, web design and business development.

Skills: planning, strategy, data driven decisions and analytics, innovation, agile methodologies, sales oriented, business development, online distribution.

Keywords: Online Marketing, Ecommerce, Revenue Management, Scrum, University Professor, E-Commerce, Startups, Travel Geek, Business Strategy

Experience

E-Commerce Corporate Manager at Libertador Hotels, Resorts & Spas

November 2015 - Present

In charge of 8 hotels. Responsible for creating and maintaining a corporate ecommerce strategy that maximizes retail conversion opportunities for Libertador branded hotels and ensuring all Starwood-Legacy (now Marriott) franchised hotels (Westin Lima, Paracas Luxury Collection, Tambo del Inka Luxury Collection, Palacio del Inka Luxury Collection) are aligning with corporate ecommerce strategies, e-activating electronic channels to maximize online revenue and profitability, providing local market insights and recommendations and verifying all hotels within the cluster are fully activating and optimizing their presence on approved online channels. Successful development and optimization of direct and indirect online sales channels. Agile methodologies, SCRUM and kanvan-based task force projects.

Associate Professor, Thesis advisor and Tutor at Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas August 2012 - Present

Market Associate at Expedia, Inc.

October 2014 - November 2015 (1 year 2 months)

Editor in Chief & Founder at ROM.PE

November 2009 - October 2015 (6 years)

Marketing at Hilton Lima Miraflores

February 2014 - September 2014 (8 months)

General Manager at Neo Humano Group

July 2013 - January 2014 (7 months)

Revenue Management at Belmond

March 2012 - July 2013 (1 year 5 months)

Technical Advisor & Auditor at Cenfotur

August 2012 - December 2012 (5 months)

Senior Marketing Executive, Hotels, Peru at Belmond

October 2011 - February 2012 (5 months)

Marketing Analyst, Hotels, Peru at Belmond

May 2008 - September 2011 (3 years 5 months)

Coorganizador General / General Co-organizer at Lima Valley

January 2010 - December 2010 (1 year)

Education

Cornell University

Master Certificate in Hospitality Management, Team dynamics, Finance, Marketing, Hotel

Revenue, 2011 - 2011

Universidad Tecnológica del Perú

Master's degree, Sales, Distribution, and Marketing Operations, General, 2016 - 2018

Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas

Marketing, Marketing, Research, Internet Marketing, 2008 - 2015

Activities and Societies: President & Founder of the project "Peru 3.0", a branding approach to position Peru as a country of wonders, Delegates Group, Photography Club

Honors and Awards

Recognition letter for great teaching on Ecommerce Graduate course, Employee of the Year, Employee of November & December 2010, Distinguished Service Award, 1st. place in the general entrance test

Lynn Mora

 $\hbox{E-Commerce Corporate Manager at Libertador Hotels, Resorts \& Spas + Digital \, Disruptor + Travel \, Geek}$

lynnmora@gmail.com



Contact Lynn on LinkedIn